Epris Harris-Burnett

Front-End / React Web Developer

Web developer with experience in service and eCommerce based web applications. Knowledgeable in UI/UX and retaining both when building out the front-end, as well as maintaining accessibility. Passionate about making complex technology seem simple and functional to its consumer.

eharrisburnett@gmail.com

Cornelius, NC, USA

in linkedin.com/in/LINKEDIN.COM/IN/EPRISHB

248.730.8645

eprishb.github.io/
github.com/eprishb



Programming JavaScript Frameworks/Libr React Languages aries

Web HTML/CSS, responsive web design, Database MongoDB, Firebase

accessibility (WAI-ARIA)

Marketing HubSpot, Google Analytics, Google Search Console, Google Tag Manager



WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer & Graphic Designer BROOKS EQUIPMENT / BHC ISS

02/2019 - Present

Fire & Life Safety Redistributor, and Technician Training Center

Achievements/Tasks

- Collaborated with IT in building two eCommerce sites and a service site from the ground up.
- Increased web traffic by 6 7% by applying fundamental SEO strategy with the support of the marketing team.
- Migrated an eCommerce site using URL mapping, implementing Schema/structured data, ensuring proper use of meta tags, and updating the sitemap.
- Adapted Google Marketing Platform. (Analytics, Tag Manager) and Google Search Console into eCommerce sites for eCommerce tracking and SEO.
- Perform web maintenance on 7 company sites including making older sites accessible, mobile-friendly, optimized for search engines and redeveloping the site when UI/UX needs to be updated.
- Integrate HubSpot into sites for automated email, marketing processes, and form capturing.

Graphic Designer BRADLEY CO.

Promotional Merchandising Agency

Southfield, MI

Charlotte, NC

Achievements/Tasks

- Managed up to 20+ projects simultaneously, including rush orders, with deadlines of 24 hours or less.
- Created presentations for web store advertisement banners for various clients.
- Curated email blasts for PPG Paint yearly calendars via MailChimp and Illustrator.

1/2



WORK EXPERIENCE

Project ManagerAPPLET SOCIAL (I AM Creative LLC)

09/2014 - 05/2018 Creative Solutions Detroit, MI

 Graphic Designer CONTINENTAL SERVICES

> 09/2012 - 09/2014 Dining & Catering

Troy, MI



PERSONAL PROJECTS

iLL Follow - MERN Social Media Application (06/2021 - Present) ☑

- Social media application for a non-profit startup. Set to launch fall 2022.
- CRUD operations.
- MongoDB.

Memory Game - JavaScript Application ☑

- Gained solid understanding of OOP, JavaScript methods, and properties
- Git & GitHub

My Reads - React Application 🕜

- Implement "React Thinking" and design patterns.
- REST API + Fetch.

Neighborhood Map - React Application

- APIs (Google Maps and Foursquare).
- Node.js and npm packages.
- Regular Expressions.



CERTIFICATES

NANODEGREE - Front-End Web Development (11/2018 - Present) ☑

Udactiy - Grow with Google Scholarship



EDUCATION

 BFA Graphic Design Southern New Hampshire University

09/2018 - 12/2018